In every good, there is evil. In Holly Gooding
there is something worse. Much worse.
Doppelganger is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Avi Nesher.
After being implicated in a murder, a young woman flees New York City and
moves to Los Angeles, where she rents a room from a writer.
They begin an affair, but it seems she's been followed
by a homicidal duplicate of herself.
Holly Gooding, played by Drew Barrymore.
Patrick Highsmith, played by George Newbern.
Doctor Heller, played by Dennis Christopher.
Elizabeth, played by Leslie Hope.
Sister Jan, played by Sally Kellerman.
Mike Wallace, played by George Maharis.
Doppelganger (also known as Doppelganger: The Evil Within) is a 1993 American supernatural horror
thriller film written and directed by Avi Nesher, starring Drew Barrymore and George Newbern.
The film premiered at the Avoriaz Fantastic Film Festival in January
1993, where it was nominated for the "Grand Prize" award.
It was released on VHS on May 26, 1993 in the United States.
This was George Maharis' final film before his death in May 2023.
The film explores themes of nightmare, roommates, seduction, stalker, murder.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.